holidog.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy

Print this page 

Last Updated July 07, 2013 

### 1.Use of Information

Holidog, Inc. ("Holidog","we","our","us") takes your privacy seriously. We have established this Privacy Policy to carefully explain how we gather and disseminate information provided to us by you. By accessing our website us.holidog.com ("website" and/or "Site"), you acknowledge and agree to comply with this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, which can be found at http://us.holidog.com/Legal/ConditionsOfUse. Unless otherwise defined herein, the terms in this Privacy Policy have the same meaning as in our Terms of Service. You acknowledge that we gather information from you, our users, customers and those who visit the Site subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Our primary goal in collecting and using information is to improve our services and the Site. When you first set up an account with Holidog you will be asked for certain information that will be used to create your profile. The profile will generally contain first name, last name, motivation, pictures, and availability. This information will be publicly available on the Site. 

### 2.Personally Identifiable Information

Our objective is to provide you with exceptional service and an excellent website experience. To do so, we collect personally identifiable information about you that you provide to us while using the website. Personal Data includes information that can identify a user as a specific individual, such as, without limitation, your name, physical address, phone number, credit card number or e-mail address, cookies (defined below), IP logs and other information that is required to process your account, create your profile or use our services or respond to certain requests ("Personal Data"). We also collect non-personally identifiable information, which may be linked to the user's Personal Data, including the user's login name and IP address through the user's interactions with the site. Third parties may collect non-personally identifiable information on our website and we have no control over their access and use of such information. 

### 3.Sharing Information

We only share Personal Data as provided in this policy or with your consent. Holidog may share your Personal Data with its parents, subsidiaries and with third party service providers to transact business that we, in our sole discretion, deem reasonable. Also, if you post personal nformation or any information to a public area on the Site, it is no longer personal information for purposes of this privacy policy and Holidog has no control over the dissemination of such information. If you decide to share your personal information with other users of the Site, such as your email address or telephone number, Holidog has no control over whethers others collect, use, or share such information without your consent. 

### 4.Messages sent through Holidog.com

Holidog has developed a unique forum for its users to communicate with each other and with Holidog. If the user provides emails to which the user want the message to be sent, Holidog will have access to such email addresses and will only use them for the purpose of sending such message. YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE AND ITS INTERNAL MESSAGING SYSTEM MEANS YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOUR MESSAGES ARE NOT PRIVATE. FURTHER YOU CONSENT FOR US TO MAKE REVISIONS, SAVE, EDIT, REFUSE TO TRANSMIT, AND OTHERWISE USE THE MESSAGES OR ITS CONTENT, OR DISCLOSE THE MESSAGES TO THIRD PARTIES, IN OUR SOLE DISCRETION. 

### 5.Third Parties and Service Providers

In order yo provide you with certain services, we may share your Personal Data with our subsidiaries, parent companies or service providers. When you access our website to take advantage of our services, we may have to share your information with service providers (i.e, to conduct database management, web analytics, or improve the Site's technical capabilities). For suppliers and service providers' privacy policies and other information, please refer to their respective policies. Holidog is not responsible for the use, collection or transmittal of any of your Personal Data by such third parties. 

### 6.Cookies

Holidog's website uses "cookie" technology and allows third parties to use cookie technology. Cookies are pieces of code that allow for personalization of the website experience by saving your information such as user ID and other preferences. You can delete those cookies by following your browser's instructions but this may change your experience in our website requiring you to input all the information again when you re-visit the website. 

### 7.Phising

Holidog is very concerned with identity theft and the practice currently known as "phising". Please be aware that you will not receive at any time unsolicited e-mails or phone calls requesting your account ID and password, credit card information or national identification numbers. For more information about the practice of phising and its dangers, visit the Federal Trade Commission's website at [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/). 

### 8.Policy towards Children

Holidog does not knowingly collect Personal Data or any personally identifiable information from persons under the age of 16. Holidog does not knowingly allow persons under the age of 13 to use the website. Persons under 16 are not allowed to use the webiste. 

### 9.Law Enforcement Compliance

Holidog reserves the right to release some or all of your Personal Data to comply with applicable law and when disclosure is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. We may also release Personal Data to enforce or apply the terms and conditions applicable to our products and services, protect us or others against fraudulent or inappropriate activities, or otherwise protect the rights, property or safety of our website, our affiliated companies, our customers, or others. 

### 10.Security

Holidog makes every effort to secure the Site and put in place electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect on our Site. However, you acknowledge that no method of information transmission over the Internet, or method of data storage, is ever 100% secure. Therefore, Holidog does not and cannot guarantee the safety of any Personal Data or other information on the Site. When sharing information over open networks such as the Internet or email, be mindful that such information can be lost or accessed by others. We are not liable for losses, direct or indirect, caused by security breaches on information shared over open networks. 

### 11.Information Control

Holidog makes it a priority to maintain the integrity of our website. We maintain the right to remove information on the website that contains misleading information or unsubstantiated claims, hateful, biased, or discriminating speech, or information that is contradictory with Holidog's mission and values. Holidog does not knowingly or intentionally include links to others websites that contain hatefull speech, bias, or discriminatory conduct. 

### 12.Business Transfers

In the future, Holidog may sell or buy others companies and Personal Data may be transferred as part of these transactions. Moreover, another company may acquire Holidog by merger, sale of assets or otherwise and Personal Data may be transferred as part of such a transaction. 

### 13.Links to Other Sites

Our website may contain links to other websites maintained by third parties. We do not have control over information you share on third-party websites. They have their own privacy policies and it is your responsability to keep your information private when accessing these websites. When you click on such links you will leave Holidog's website and will be subject to third party's privacy policy. Holidog cannot guarantee any information contained on those websites and is not liable for any of such content. Holidog does not and cannot authorize the use of copyrighted materials on such third-party websites. If you receive information transmitted from third-party websites, Holidog is not liable or responsible for the security of such information. 

### 14.International Use of the Site

Our service is hosted and provided from Chicago, USA. If you access and use our site from the European Union or other geographic region outside the United States with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from US law, please note that are transferring your personal data to the United States and different data protection laws may apply. By providing your Personal Data, you consent to the transfer of your personally identifiable information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

### 15.Contact Information

We welcome feedback concerning our website and services. By using us.holidog.com you consent to our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or wish to opt out from receiving messages sent by us, please contact us at:   
Name: Julien Muller   
Email: contact@holidog.com

### 16.Changes To Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to update or modify our Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes or updates will be reflected on our website under "Privacy Policy". Any updated Privacy Policy will apply to information already gathered before the time of the change and any new information. In order to be aware of our policies that may affect you and your privacy, we suggest you refer to our Privacy Policy periodically. 

Please be aware that any information you post on our Site in a public area of the Site is not Personal Data and/or personally information for purposes of this Privacy Policy. Holidog does not control how others may collect, use or disclose such information.
